Guide to the Trade catalogs collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- S
  - Sky Specialties Corporation (Detroit, Mich.), undated; Uai Sk91; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3331)
    Heywood starter
  - Slack Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1935–1938; Uai SL11; 4 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3332-3335)
    Party supplies and decorations
  - Slaymaker, Barry and Company (Lancaster, Pa.), 1894; Uai SL19; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3336)
    Padlocks, etc.
  - Sleeman Gas Saving Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1886–1892; Uai SL24; 2 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3337)
    Automatic gas governor
  - Sligo Iron Store Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1904; Uai SL35; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3338)
  - Sloan and Chace Manufacturing Company, Ltd. (Newark, N.J.), 1895; Uai SL52; 5 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3339)
    Watch and clock machinery, etc.
  - Sloane-Blabon Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1952; Uai +SL525; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3340)
    Linoleum products
  - Slocomb, J. T., Company (Providence, R.I.), undated; Uai SL53; 2 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3341)
    Machinists' tools
  - Sly, W. W., Manufacturing Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1937; Uai +SL91; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3342)
    Dust control systems
  - Smart, James (Brockville, Ontario), 1878–1879; Uai Sm28; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3343)
  - Smead Manufacturing Company (Hastings, Minn.), 1913; Uai Sm31; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3344)
    Filing envelopes
  - Smith Gas Engineering Company (Dayton, Ohio), 1918–1921; Uai +Sm677; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3361)
    Gas
  - Smith Premier Typewriter Company (Syracuse, N.Y.), 1890–1903; Uai Sm68; 4 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3367)
  - Smith Premier Typewriter Company, Inc. (Syracuse, N.Y.), 1909; Uai Sm681; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3368)
  - Smith Wheel Chair Concern (New York, N.Y.), 1878; Uai +Sm69; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3370)
    Wheelchairs, etc.
  - Smith and Anthony Stove Company (Boston, Mass.), 1885–1887; Uai Sm65; 2 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3354)
    Heating and ventilating systems, fire places, etc.
  - Smith and Beck (London, England), 1851; Uai Sm653; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3355)
    Achromatic microscopes, etc.
  - Smith and Shaw Electric Company (New York, N.Y.), 1883; Uai Sm66; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3356)
    Electric dumb bell, etc.
  - Smith and Sherman (New Haven, Conn.), undated; Uai +Sm662; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3357)
    Olmsted's anthracite stoves
  - Smith and Thayer Company (Boston, Mass.), 1905; Uai Sm665; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3358)
    Water supply goods
  - Smith and Wesson (Springfield, Mass.), 1921; 3 volumes (Box 399, Folder 4357)
    Firearms
  - Smith and Wesson, Inc. (Springfield, Mass.), 1914–1926; Uai +Sm67; 3 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3359)
    Revolvers and pistols
  - Smith, Beck and Beck (London, England), 1859; Uai Sm675; 2 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3360)
  - Smith, F. E., and Company (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1874; Uai Sm56; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3345)
    Flour, etc.
  - Smith, Geo. A., and Company (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai Sm57; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3346)
    Chemical, microscopical, and philosophical apparatus
  - Smith, George A. and Company (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai Sm6775; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3362)
  - Smith, Gray and Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1908; Uai +Sm678; 2 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3363-3364)
    Servants' livery, motor clothing, etc.
  - Smith, H. B., Company (New York, N.Y., Westfield, Mass.), Uai +Sm578
    Boilers, radiators, etc.
    - 1884–1916, 8 volumes (Box 303, Folder 3618-3622)
    - 1924, 1 volume (Box 304)
  - Smith, H. B., Company, Inc. (Westfield, Mass.), 1902–1939; Uai +Sm579; 2 volumes (Box 305, Folder 3623-3624)
    Char-wood heaters, wood working machinery
  - Smith, H. B., Machine Company (Smithville, N.J.), 1884–1888; Uai +Sm58; 4 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3349)
  - Smith, H. B., and Company (New York, N.Y., Westfield, Mass.), 1872–1875; Uai Sm577; 3 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3347-3348)
    Steam and water heating apparatus
  - Smith, Howard A., and Company (Newark, N.J.), 1886; Uai Sm6781; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3365)
    Bicycles, tricycles, and cycling goods
  - Smith, J. Gibb, and Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1889; Uai Sm62; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3351)
    Mouldings
  - Smith, J. Finley (New York, N.Y.), 1881; Uai Sm61; 1 volume (Box 278, Folder 3350)
  - Smith, Perry L. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1911; Uai +Sm6791; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3366)
    Trunks, leather goods, and umbrellas
  - Smith, Richardson Company (Attleboro, Mass.), 1916; Uai Sm685; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3369)
    Polishing, tubbing, and drying out machines
  - Smith, T. L., Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1924; Uai +Sm64; 2 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3352)
    Concrete mixers and pavers
  - Smith, Winfield H., Corporation (Springville, N.Y.), 1947–1948; Uai Sm645; 2 volumes (Box 278, Folder 3353)
    Speed reducers
  - Smyth, James, and Son (Peasenhall, Suffolk, England), 1878; Uai +Sm97; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3371)
  - Smyth, John M. (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai +Sm972; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3372)
    Household furnishings
  - Snap-on Tools Corporation (Kenosha, Wis.), 1942–1948; Uai +Sn14; 3 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3373-3375)
  - Snow, A. W., and Company (Boston, Mass.), 1894–1898; Uai +Sn62; 2 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3378-3379)
    Stable fixtures, etc.
  - Snow, E. W., and Company (Rochester, N.Y.), 1923; Uai Sn61; 2 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3376)
    Refilled fuses
  - Snow, L. T. (New Haven, Conn.), 1899; Uai Sn615; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3377)
  - Snyder's, Ward B. (New York, N.Y.), undated; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4358)
    Sportsmen's goods, firearms, etc.
  - Snyder, H. P., Manufacturing Company (Little Falls, N.Y.), 1900; Uai Sn92; 3 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3380-3381)
  - Society Brand Hat Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1935; Uai So14; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3389)
    Caps
  - Società Italiana Ernesto Breda pre Construzioni Meccaniche (Milan, Italy), 1939; Uai +So13; 2 volumes (Box 318)
    Railcars
  - Société Anonyme des Acieries du Saut du Tarn (Saut du Tarn, France), undated; Uai So115; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3382)
    Steel tools, etc.
  - Société Anonyme des usines Renault, 1939; Uai +So135; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3388)
  - Société Gallois and Cie (Lyon, France), 1935; Uai +So12; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3383)
  - Société Genevoise pour la Construction des Instruments de Physique (Geneva, Switzerland), 1886; Uai +So126; 3 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3386-3387)
  - Société Générale d'Électricité, 1878; Uai So122; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3384)
    Electric bulbs
  - Société Générale des Revêtements Métalliques (Paris, France), 1866; Uai +So124; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3385)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1935–1943; Uai +So15; 18 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3390-3395)
    Oil and gas
  - Soennecken, F. (Bonn, Germany, etc.), 1913; Uai +So21; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3396)
  - Soest, Louis, and Company m.b.H. (Düsseldorf, Germany), 1929–1930; Uai +So22; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3397)
  - Soleil, H. (Paris, France), 1867; Uai So43; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3398)
  - Soltmann, E. G. (New York, N.Y.), 1890; Uai +So48; 1 volume (Box 319)
  - Sonora Phonograph Sales Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai So59; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3399)
    Alarm bells
  - Sonotone Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1944; Uai +So595; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3400)
    Military supplies
  - South Bend Lathe Works (South Bend, Ind.), 1918–1938; Uai +So87; 9 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3401-3403)
    Machine shop equipment
  - South Bend Machine Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1911; Uai +So872; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3404)
    Cement brick machines, concrete mixers, and gas engines
  - South Bend Machine Tool Company (South Bend, Ind.), 1912; Uai So873; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3405)
  - Southern Pine Association (New Orleans, La.), undated; Uai So88; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3406)
    Southern yellow pine lumber
  - Southwark Foundry and Machine Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1883–1896; Uai So89; 2 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3407-3408)
    Porter-Allen automatic engine, etc.
  - Soyer and Company (London, England), 1850; Uai So96; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3409)
    Stove and apparatus for outdoor cooking
  - Spalding, A. G., and Brothers (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1892–1938; Uai +Sp16; 4 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3410)
    Bicycles, sportswear, and sporting goods, etc.
  - Sparklets Corporation (Irvington, N.J.), 1939; Uai +Sp26; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3411)
    "Sparklet" syphon
  - Spaulding Print Paper Company (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai Sp28; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3412)
    Drafting room supplies, drawing materials, mathematical and engineering instruments
  - Spear and Jackson (New York, N.Y.), 1869; Uai Sp31; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3413)
    Saws, files, and edge tools
  - Special Chemicals Company (Highland Park, Ill.), 1923; Uai Sp318; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3414)
    "Pfanstiehl" chemicals
  - Specialty Manufacturing Company (Watertown, Conn.), 1896; Uai Sp32; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3415)
    Door knobs, etc.
  - Speeder Cycle Company (New Castle, Ind.), 1897; Uai Sp325; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3416)
  - Spencer Heater Company (Williamsport, Pa.), 1926; Uai Sp363; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3421)
  - Spencer Lens Company (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1896–1935; Uai Sp366; 6 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3422-3423)
  - Spencer Turbine Cleaner Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1929–1937; Uai +Sp369; 10 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3424-3425)
    Vacuum cleaning apparatus
  - Spencer and Son (Dublin, Ireland), undated; Uai Sp36; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3420)
    Local heliostat
  - Spencer, H. R., Optical Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1889; Uai Sp34; 2 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3418)
    Microscope objectives, optical goods, etc.
  - Spencer, S. M. Manufacturing Company (Boston, Mass.), 1923; Uai Sp345; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3419)
    Letter cutters, die sinkers, engravers, etc.
  - Sperling, Otto (Stuttgart, Germany), 1931; Uai +Sp375; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3426)
    Language courses
  - Sperry Gyroscope Company, Inc. (Great Neck, N.Y.), 1912–1944; Uai +Sp388; 21 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3429-3435)
    Gyro-compasses, mechanical steering systems, etc.
  - Sperry and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1883; Uai Sp384; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3428)
  - Sperry, D. R., and Company (Batavia, Ill.), 1910; Uai Sp38; 2 volumes (Box 279, Folder 3427)
    Filter press
  - Spiedel, J. G. (Reading, Pa.), 1923; Uai Sp33; 1 volume (Box 279, Folder 3417)
    Elevators and hoisting machinery
  - Spiers, Richard N. (New York, N.Y.), 1899; Uai +Sp44; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3436)
    Stained, leaded, and mosaic glass
  - Spindler and Hoyer (Göttingen, Germany), 1900–1916; Uai +Sp46; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3437)
    Mechanical instruments, etc.
  - Spirit Purifying and Aging Company (Boston, Mass.), 1884; Uai Sp48; 2 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3438)
    Apparatus for purifying and aging distilled spirits
  - Sponge Rubber Products Company (Shelton, Conn.), undated; Uai +Sp66; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3439)
    Cellular rubber and bonded fibrous materials
  - Sprague Electric Railway and Motor Company (New York, N.Y.), 1890; Uai Sp74; 2 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3441)
    Sprague automatic motors, etc.
  - Sprague Electrical Supplies, Inc. (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1942; Uai +Sp742; 1 volume (Box 320)
    Electrical supplies and equipment
  - Sprague Mowing Machine Company (Providence, R.I.), 1871; Uai Sp75; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3442)
    Mowing machinery
  - Sprague, H. M. (Parishville, N.Y.), 1890; Uai Sp73; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3440)
  - Spratts Patent (America) Limited (New York, N.Y.), 1886; Uai Sp77; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3443)
    Spratts patent "Fibrine" dog food, poultry and game food, etc.
  - Spring and Buckley, Inc. (New Britain, Conn.), 1940; Uai +Sp81; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3444)
    Electrical controls
  - Springfield Bicycle Manufacturing Company (Boston, Mass., etc.), 1889; Uai Sp84; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3445)
  - Springfield Wire Screen Company (Springfield, Ill.), 1899; Uai Sp85; 2 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3446)
    Screen doors and windows
  - Squibb, E. R., and Sons (Brooklyn, N.Y., etc.), 1892–1940; Uai +Sq411; 15 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3450-3453)
    Pharmaceutical preparations
  - Squibb, Edward R. (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1883–1891; Uai Sq41; 15 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3447-3449)
  - Squier, George L., Manufacturing Company (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1879–1939; Uai +Sq45; 6 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3455-3456)
    Plantation machinery
  - Squier, George L., and Brother (Buffalo, N.Y.), undated; Uai Sq44; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3454)
    Sugar cane machinery
  - St. Alban's Grain Company (St. Albans, Vt.), 1921; Uai Sa22; 1 volume (Box 276, Folder 3171)
    Chicken feed, etc.
  - St. Joseph Motor Company (St. Joseph, Mich.), 1909; Uai +Sa23; 1 volume (Box 276, Folder 3172)
    "Miss Simplicity" marine motors
  - St. Lawrence River Skiff, Canoe and Steam Launch Company (Clayton, N.Y.), 1880; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4348)
    Canoes, etc.
  - St. Louis Iron and Machine Works (St. Louis, Mo.), 1894; Uai Sa24; 1 volume (Box 276, Folder 3173)
    "St. Louis Corliss" engine, etc.
  - St. Louis Refrigerator and Wooden Gutter Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1895; Uai Sa243; 1 volume (Box 276, Folder 3174)
    "Lu-Mi-Num" aluminum bicycles
  - Staatsgut., K., Ackergeräthe-Fabrik (Schleissheim, Germany), 1854; Uai St113; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3457)
  - Stade, Geo. (Berlin, Germany), 1894–1910; Uai St115; 19 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3458-3459)
    Stills and sugar-refining machinery
  - Stadler, Max, and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1885; Uai St12; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3460)
  - Stafford, C. W. (New York, N.Y.), 1867; Uai St13; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3462)
    Wooden pavement
  - Stahl, William (Quincy, Ill.), 1891; Uai +St14; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3463)
    "Excelsior" spraying outfits
  - Stalker Manufacturing Company (New York, N.Y.), 1911; Uai St17; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3464)
    Horse bits and specialties
  - Stallman, Frank A. (Columbus, Ohio), 1900; Uai St18; 2 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3465)
    Dresser trunks, travel cases, etc.
  - Standard Car Heating and Ventilating Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1884; Uai +St22; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3466)
    Car heaters and ventilators
  - Standard Chain Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900; Uai St222; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3467)
  - Standard Electric Tool Company (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1913; Uai +St226; 2 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3468)
  - Standard Emery and Polishing Wheel Company (Springfield, Mass.), 1904; Uai St228; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3469)
    Polishing wheels, etc.
  - Standard Empire Vacuum Brake Company (New York, N.Y.), 1880; Uai +St229; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3470)
    Railcar brakes, etc.
  - Standard Folding Bed Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +St231; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3471)
  - Standard Garden Tractors (Minneapolis, Minn.), undated; Uai St2311; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3472)
  - Standard Gas Equipment Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1937; Uai +St2328; 3 volumes (Box 280, Folder 3474)
    Gas cooking equipment
  - Standard Gas Light Works Manufacturing Company (New York, N.Y.), 1883; Uai St232; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3473)
    Illuminating gas for residences
  - Standard Gauge Steel Company (Beaver Falls, Pa.), 1904; Uai St233; 1 volume (Box 280, Folder 3475)
    Machine keys, machine rack, elevator guides, etc.
  - Standard Machine Company (Holyoke, Mass.), 1896; Uai St236; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3476)
    Grinding and polishing machinery
  - Standard Manufacturing Company (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1909; Uai St2365; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3477)
    Telephones
  - Standard Motor Company, Ltd. (Coventry, England), 1933; Uai St237; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3478)
  - Standard Oil Company of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1922–1934; Uai +St24; 8 volumes (Box 322)
    Motor oils, etc.
  - Standard Oil Fuel Burner Company (Fort Plain, N.Y.), 1891; Uai +St241; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3479)
    Hydro-carbon burners
  - Standard Roller Bearing Company (New York, N.Y.), 1916; Uai St243; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3480)
    Brinell meter
  - Standard Sanitary Manufacturing Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904–1908; Uai +St244; 2 volumes (Box 281, Folder 3481-3482)
  - Standard Scale and Supply Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1912; Uai St246; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3483)
    "Standard" scales, etc.
  - Standard Scientific Company (New York, N.Y.), 1912–1921; Uai St247; 3 volumes (Box 281, Folder 3484-3486)
    Scientific instruments and laboratory supplies, Laboratory apparatus
  - Standard Sewing Machine Company (Cleveland, Ohio), undated; Uai St248; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3487)
  - Standard Sheet Metal Manufacturing Company (Washington, Pa.), 1913; Uai St25; 2 volumes (Box 281, Folder 3488)
    Lockers and cases, etc.
  - Standard Steel Car Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1905; Uai St25a; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3489)
    Railways, etc.
  - Standard Steel Works Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1907; Uai St25o; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3491)
    Steel tires
  - Standard Steel and Bearings, Inc. (Plainville, Conn.), 1932; Uai St25b; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3490)
  - Standard Supply Company (New York, N.Y.), 1917; Uai St251; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3492)
    Supplies for hospitals, offices, etc.
  - Standard Textile Products Company, 1925; Uai +St2511; 1 volume (Box 323)
    Sanitas wall coverings
  - Standard Thermometer and Electric Company (Peabody, Mass.), undated; Uai St252; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3493)
    Enclosed arc lamps and metallic thermometers
  - Standard Tool Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1923–1928; Uai St255; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3494)
    Milling cutters, twist drills, reamers, etc.
  - Standard Welding Company (New York, N.Y.), 1941; Uai +St256; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3495)
    Automobile rims
  - Standard X-Ray Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1933; Uai +St26; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3496)
    X-Ray equipment
  - Stanley Works (New Britain, Conn., etc.), 1916–1939; Uai +St27; 10 volumes (Box 306, Folder 3625-3629)
    Wrought steel hardware
  - Star Brass Manufacturing Company (Boston, Mass.), 1908; Uai St28; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3497)
    "Star" gages
  - Star Drilling Machine Company (Akron, Ohio), 1911; Uai St282; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3498)
    Drilling machinery
  - Star Expansion Bolt Company (New York, N.Y.), 1915; Uai St284; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3499)
    "Sebco" products
  - Star Heel Plate Company (Newark, N.J.), 1911; Uai +St286; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3500)
    Heel plates, etc.
  - Starrett, L. S., Company (Athol, Mass.), 1918–1937; Uai St29; 9 volumes (Box 281, Folder 3501-3506)
    Mechanical tools
  - Stearns, A. T., Lumber Company (Boston, Mass.), 1915; Uai +St31; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3507)
    Mantels, columns, doors, sash, cabinet work, etc.
  - Stearns, E. C., and Company (Syracuse, N.Y.), 1897–1899; Uai +St32; 2 volumes (Box 281, Folder 3508)
    "Yellow Fellow" bicycles
  - Stearns, F. B., Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1909–1916; Uai +St325; 9 volumes (Box 281, Folder 3509-3511)
  - Steel Furniture Company (Grand Rapids, Mich.), 1930; Uai +St34; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3513)
    Theatre seating
  - Steel and Tubes, Inc. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1933; Uai St33; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3512)
    Electric weld tubing
  - Steinheil, C. A. (Munich, Germany), 1857–1867; Uai St36; 4 volumes (Box 281, Folder 3514)
    Astronomical and optical instruments
  - Steinheil, C. A., Söhne (Munich, Germany), 1907; Uai +St361; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3515)
  - Steinmüller, L. u. C. (Gummersbach, Germany), 1919; Uai St37; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3516)
    Fire-stop
  - Stemmler, L. E. (Long Island, N.Y.), 1937; Uai St38; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3517)
    Bows, arrows, and archery tackle
  - Stender, W. P. (Leipzig, Germany), 1895; Uai St42; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3518)
  - Stendicke, Aug. (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai St425; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3519)
  - Stephan, C. H., Manufacturing Company (Springfield, Ohio), undated; Uai St43; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3520)
    "Star" carbon emery wheel dresser
  - Stephens-Adamson Manufacturing Company (Aurora, Ill.), 1904; Uai St44; 1 volume (Box 281, Folder 3521)
    Elevating, conveying and power transmitting machinery
  - Stephenson, John, Company (Elizabeth, N.J.), 1905; Uai +St45; 1 volume (Box 324)
  - Sterling Blower Company (Hartford, Conn.), undated; Uai St458; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3522)
    Blowers and blower systems
  - Sterling Brass Company (Cleveland, Ohio), undated; Uai +St459; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3523)
    Brass and specialties
  - Sterling Company (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1858; Uai St46; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3524)
    "Sterling" gas regulator
  - Sterling-Meaker Company (Newark, N.J.), 1907; Uai +St463; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3525)
    Fenders, etc.
  - Stetson, John B., Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1925–1926; Uai St47; 3 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3526)
    "Stetson" hats
  - Steuben Glass, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai St475; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3527)
  - Stevens, B. A. (Toledo, Ohio), 1889–1890; Uai +St48; 2 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3528)
    Refrigerators, Butchers' supplies and machinery
  - Stevens, J., Arms and Tool Company (Chicopee Falls, Mass.), undated; Uai St482; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3529)
  - Stevens-Duryea Company (Chicopee Falls, Mass.), Uai +St484
    Motor cars, etc.
    - 1912, 31 volumes (Box 307, Folder 3630)
    - undated, 1 volume (Box 308)
    - undated, 1 volume (Box 309)
    - undated, 1 volume (Box 310)
  - Stevens-Duryea Company (Chicopee Falls, Mass.), 1914; Uai St485; 6 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3530-3531)
  - Steward, J. H. (London, England), 1862; Uai St49; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3532)
  - Stewart Iron Works (Cincinnati, Ohio), undated; Uai +St52; 2 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3534)
    Iron fence, etc.
  - Stewart Speed Indicator Factory (Chicago, Ill.), 1914; Uai +St525; 1 volume (Box 325)
    Speedometer, etc.
  - Stewart, F. L. (Murrysville, Pa.), 1880; Uai St515; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3533)
    Sugar
  - Stiles, A. C., Anti-Friction Metal Company (Baltimore, Md., New Haven, Conn.), 1908; Uai St53; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3535)
    A. C. Stiles patent car journal bearings
  - Stilwell, L. W. (Deadwood, S. D.), 1908; Uai +St535; 2 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3536)
    Gems, minerals, etc.
  - Stilz, Louis E., and Brother Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1938–1941; Uai St54; 7 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3537)
    Flags, military, naval and theatrical goods, etc.
  - Stinson, Edward, and Company (Baltimore, Md.), 1903; Uai St57; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3538)
    Solid rubber tires
  - Stirlen Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1928; Uai +St58; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3539)
    Piezo oscillator cabinets
  - Stockbridge Machine Company (Worcester, Mass.), undated; Uai St62; 2 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3540)
    Crank shaper, etc.
  - Stoddard Manufacturing Company (Dayton, Ohio), undated; Uai +St64; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3541)
    "Tiger" and "Tigress" bicycles
  - Stoedtner, Dr. Franz (Berlin, Germany), undated; Uai St65; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3542)
    Projection apparatus
  - Stoelting, C. H., Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1907–1909; Uai +St67; 2 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3544-3545)
    Scientific apparatus and laboratory apparatus
  - Stone and Andrew Inc. (Boston, Mass., New York, N.Y.), 1917; Uai St72; 2 volumes (Box 282, Folder 3547)
    Paper and specialties
  - Stone and Webster Engineering Corporation (Seattle, Washington), 1912; Uai St715; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3546)
    Electric railways, etc.
  - Stone-Lloyd System, 1904; Uai +St721; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3548)
    Ships
  - Stoneware Pipe Company (Alton Junction, Ill.), 1888; Uai St73; 1 volume (Box 282, Folder 3549)
    Culvert and sewer pipe